Start moving in!
Is anyone there? →Is anyone there?
If anyone is there, please respond.
Is anyone there?
Please help me.
Rescuer in need of help!
Found him!
《Ichiro, are you okay?
I'll save you now.
＜That day...
I saved the life of a father and son.
《《Ichiro.
Your children will be fine, too.
It's almost here.
Excuse me, please!
Transport, please.
Yes, sir.
Chief Inspector Nakagawa
I received a call from the command center.
His wife was taken to Kawagoe Chuo Hospital.
She was rushed to Kawagoe Chuo Hospital.
What?
Truth?
＜And that day...
＜I lost someone I loved.
Why...?
＜My wife, who saw me off with such a cheerful smile...
"with such a cheerful smile...
＜He died of an acute myocardial infarction.
Good morning.
I'll be ready for you soon...
I did it again.
＜All alone.
To the daughter who lost her beloved mother.
<Together we will do our best
＜I don't remember talking to him.
＜But the days pass in sorrow.
<And the sadness
"faded away.
Next, this X-squared plus...
＜On school event days
I can be off-duty on school days.
<With the help of my workplace.
Welcome home.
I'm home.
＜But even that has its limits.
Sorry, Arisu.
《Day of the gymnastic festival...》
Father
I couldn't miss work.
It doesn't matter.
＜I found myself in the middle of puberty.
My daughter was in the throes of puberty.
Good morning.
You're up early again.
I'm off.
Be careful.
＜Before I knew it, the laundry was done.
＜I'll take what's mine.
<More face to face time at the dinner table.
"and face to face meals are steadily decreasing.
Good morning.
＜I thought this was the reality of fathers and daughters.
＜Well, I thought I had no choice.
＜Still...
Cute things are cute.
＜Above all...
＜I'm doing my best to take care of the house and my dreams for the future.
My daughter is doing her best in her studies.
＜I was so proud.
＜And just because...
＜I just wanted her to be happy.
Bon appétit.
（I'm going home. However...
Together.
What?
From today.
I'll live with you at home.
What?
If you don't like it, go back to your parents' house.
I'm gonna take a cab now.
No, why would you say that to me?
Why would you say that to me?
Because you're worried about the baby.
Of course you are.
That's not...
That has nothing to do with Mr. Naruse.
It's relevant.
It doesn't.
Let's just sit down.
First, your doctor.
a good friend of mine.
and
The company I work for
at a cafe owned by the company I work for.
You have a part-time job.
And...
It's gone.
There is.
I'm worried about you and the baby.
I'm worried about you.
So why is that?
That's what I'm talking about.
Why not?
I don't understand.
I know...
It's okay to ignore them, isn't it?
Yes, I think that's a good idea.
But he can't do that.
Anyway...
I'm fine now.
Please go home. Alone.
I wrote about Clay's angel painting.
High School Student
Arisu Nakagawa?
I thought I'd seen that name before.
I thought I'd seen it before.
Art Essay Contest for High School Students
I like it.
I read the award-winning books every year.
I thought your...
I thought it was funny.
The desire to be a curator
I wanted to be a curator.
Oh, okay.
I didn't want you to give up on your dream.
But you...
You're a mess if you don't.
That I'm pregnant.
And that you're hiding it from your father.
And a shady part-time job.
So...
I'll be careful from now on.
So, a suggestion.
You can choose one of the two.
You choose the one you like better.
First, I'm going home to my parents.
Tell your father about the pregnancy.
On top of that, I'm going to
I'm going home to rest for a while.
Please don't be selfish.
Second, at my house.
Live with me for a while.
I don't want you to do anything shady.
Help me do my job.
Is that...
You were saying the other day...
Yeah.
Young Artists and Curators
Curator Development Project
I'd like to hear what the young people have to say.
I need your help.
What do we do? The first one?
The second one?
Second by.
Have a safe trip down.
Yes, sir.
(Yuma) Stop.
Who is it?
What?
Are you okay?
Yes?
No, just now.
This guy gave me a really scary look.
(loud music playing)
Turn it off!
《(Music stops)
Oh... the girl who was dancing?
A friend?
No, just a neighbor.
Huh? That's terrible.
It's the same college.
You're worried about me?
It's not kidnapping or anything, is it?
Maybe half.
What?
Don't worry.
I'm the boss at my part-time job.
Really?
Yeah.
You're not getting in trouble because of the money, are you?
You're not in some kind of trouble with the money, are you?
If that's the case, I'll lend you some money.
Oh... someone has less than me...
Oh, God. Come on. Let's go.
Yes, sir.
Wow...
Eh...
Oh...
Amazing...
Feel free to look at any of them.
Are you sure?
Sure.
This...
Go ahead.
Excuse me.
Here. Use this.
Oh, it's so spacious...
Oh, and a desk to study at.
I'll have to get one.
No, you don't have to do that.
I'll figure something out.
I don't have the money to buy anything.
And it's only for a short time.
Yes?
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, did you eat dinner?
No...
Wow...
Go ahead, eat.
Yum! Yum!
Um...
Hm?
Do you have a plate or something?
Oh, yeah.
We're both going to eat it.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
You got one for Mr. Naruse?
Yes.
I'll eat here.
It's okay.
Well then...
Bon appétit.
Oh, drinks.
It's in the fridge.
Drink whatever you like.
Yes, thank you.
Well, then...
Eh...
Um... such a big place.
Do you live alone?
That's right.
Is that it, by any chance?
People who gave up on their marriages
Who gave up on marriage and bought a condominium...
I'm not giving up.
I beg your pardon.
I'm selling it when I get married.
Take good care of it, will you?
Yes, sir.
Also...
My bedroom is also my study.
It's off-limits.
Yes, sir.
And your room.
I'm not going in.
Yes, ma'am.
Also...
Tell your father about the baby.
If I knew I had an adult roommate.
And your father.
It'll give you some peace of mind, right?
After my checkup next month.
I'm going to tell you.
Not "intend," but absolutely.
Yes, sir.
Sorry.
I'm sorry I pushed you.
Ah!
It felt good.
Yes sir
Huh?
I feel like I'm forgetting something...
Ha!
I wanted to see you.
So...
"I applied for a transfer to Tokyo...
So that kiss was from you?
From you?
No...
From me?
You beat me to it.
What do you mean?
I mean...
Why did you kiss me? I just...
Ahhh...
(egg cracking)
What are you doing?
Good morning.
Morning. - Morning.
Oh, sorry.
I've taken the liberty of using it.
(The rice cooker will inform you when the rice is done cooking.)
What? You went shopping for this?
You went shopping for this?
No, I had rice and miso here.
I found some vegetables.
Oh...
I can do it in a minute.
Just a moment, please.
Amazing...
It's not an ideal breakfast.
Oh...
Go ahead.
Bon appétit!
This miso soup is so good!
Yeah.
Hi. - Hi.
Um...
In exchange for letting me live here.
I'll cook.
It's okay.
But you...
You have to take proper nutrition, right?
Just think about yourself.
I eat out a lot.
I only drink vegetable juice in the morning.
It's enough.
You really don't cook anything.
No... sometimes I do.
Anyway.
In living together.
I think it's better if we make up for each other's shortcomings.
I think it's better to make up for each other's deficiencies.
Of course, I'd rather have
Mr. Naruse is more than happy to fill in for me.
I mean, there are far more of them.
So let me at least make you some food.
Let me cook for you.
You can make it for one person, or you can make it for two.
It's the same thing.
If you want, I'm more used to two people.
All right, all right.
You're in charge of the kitchen.
But don't overdo it.
If you're not feeling well.
Don't stand in the kitchen.
Yes, sir.
I can do the shopping.
I can handle it on my own.
Mirin and Mirin-like seasoning
mirin and mirin-like seasoning.
You didn't understand.
So.
I should just buy mirin, right?
No. Mirin is too expensive.
Mirin style.
I'm paying for it.
The higher one's fine.
Oh... okay.
Then I will.
After all, the flavor is totally different.
Oh, that's right. I make lunch every day.
I bring it with me.
Shall I make one for you, too?
Shall I make one for you?
No, thank you.
If you bring a lunch box...
Who made it? I'm sure they'll ask.
"Who made this?
Oh, for Motohashi and the part-timers.
Don't tell anyone I live here.
Don't tell anyone.
If they find out, there will be a lot of trouble.
Yes, sir.
Ah.
What?
Have you already told someone?
No...
I forgot to bring my lunch box.
I forgot.
What? You scared me.
Then why don't you just buy it?
No, I can't do that.
It's such a waste. I can't do it.
I'll get it later.
Oh, then...
And while we're at it, why don't we take the desk with us?
What? No...
How did you get a desk?
What?
（Yo...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Not at all.
I'm sorry I asked so much.
No, no, no.
If Mr. Naruse asks me to do something...
Um, about what we talked about on the phone earlier...
About what we talked about on the phone earlier...
I understand.
I'm only working with Mr. Naruse personally.
I'll be sure to charge Mr. Naruse the full fee.
Mr. Naruse will be charged the full rate.
Thank you very much.
Okay, I'll get right to it.
It will be on the second floor.
What?
Why?
After my phone call with Mr. Naruse.
Just when he
I've just caught him.
Sorry I'm late.
Yeah, I just got here, too.
Thank you.
No, I...
Shall we do it?
Um... I'm sorry about yesterday.
Oh, no...
(expression of) effort or strain
(incoming vibrator)
Oh...
Yes, ma'am.
（The floor. Careful on the floor.
Okay. The one in the kitchen, right?
There it is.
Is there anything else you'd like to bring?
Then it's in the same place.
（Ouch...
☎ I'd also like a set of spoons and forks please.
what's wrong?
Oh, a set?
Okay. Bye.
Thank you.
(Vibrator notification)
What?
Oh...
(Vibrator notification)
Yes...
Good...
I'm sorry...
Let's go!
Here we go.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
（Wow.
I'm glad Kase-kun came.
This is pretty heavy, isn't it?
But your relative's daughter
That's great.
What?
This study desk.
You brought it from your parents' house, didn't you?
My kids, too.
I used to use something similar.
If you're going to stay in a room...
I'll buy you a new one.
This is the kind of solid...
It wasn't cheap.
Now it's just a piece of junk.
You have a very devoted daughter.
Oh...
Oh.
I'll take the back of that truck.
(Driver) Yes.
（This kind of thing.
How much do you think it costs?
How much is it?
Correct answer!
You can't put a price on memories.
Shall we go?
（I'll close then.
（Yes.
Oh, um, me too.
May I get in?
（Of course.
（This way then.
Oh, wait a minute.
I'll be right back.
Hey, that truck...
That truck. Follow it, please.
(Vibrator notification)
excuse me
Wow...
(DOOR OPENS)
Come in.
greeting used when entering someone's home
This room, please.
Yes, ma'am.
excuse me
（Where shall I put this?
Oh... well, let's see...
Here, please.
（Yes, well...
（Is that all right?
Thank you very much.
If you need anything else.
Please contact me anytime.
Thank you very much.
We'll be in touch.
Yes, sir.
excuse me
Oh, it's okay now.
(CHIMES)
Oh...
Yes, sir.
What?
I'm sorry to barge in like this.
You just brought it in?
It's my daughter's desk, right?
Um...
Girl.
Is he here?
What?
I've been using it since elementary school.
It's a study desk.
You can tell by the sticker on it that it's my daughter's.
I can easily tell that it's my daughter's.
The fact that it's here means that it's
The fact that it's here...
And my daughter.
That means she's here, right?
Arisu? → (e.g. "Arisu" for "Arisu")
Arisu? Are you there?
Hey, Arisu!
Um... dad.
(DOOR OPENS)
From the cab he was riding in.
I just saw the desk in the truck.
I could see it.
Mr. Naruse is here.
No, of course not.
I've taken the liberty of following you here.
I don't think it's a good thing.
Well, but... as a parent...
I don't know what's going on. I'm just...
Thank you. I'm sorry.
Um...
My daughter...
I'm in good hands here.
Is that what you mean?
Well... well, that's the way it is, isn't it?
Is that what I think it is?
I mean, you're going to have to carry it to your desk in a short amount of time.
It's not a lot of time, is it?
Is that...
What does that mean?
I recently started working part-time for my daughter.
Her supervisor.
Why do you do it?
Why do you do that?
Dad...
You shut your mouth.
I'm talking to Mr. Naruse right now.
I am a parent, and I would like to know why.
I would like to know the reason why.
I'm having a baby.
What?
Oh...
Well, congratulations on that.
To me.
I...
Pregnancy.
Scheduled on November 14.
What are you talking about?
In the belly.
I have a baby.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you before...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Is it true?
(Ichiro hitting the table with his finger)
Who's on the other side?
Who are you dealing with?
Bring him to me.
I already broke up with her.
We were together, but then we broke up...
So...
I'll give birth to her alone. I'll raise her alone.
You can't do that.
I can't do that!
What?
I don't care if you break up with him or not.
Just go get that guy.
It doesn't matter anymore.
How can it not be relevant?
Dad, please calm down.
How can I be calm?
Do you know how hard it is to have and raise a child?
Do you have any idea how hard it is to have and raise a child?
It's not easy having two parents.
And you're just a kid.
I can't do it alone.
Of course you can't.
Why do you assume it's impossible?
I've already decided.
So, what are you going to do about college?
The university you've worked so hard to get into...
And your dream of becoming a curator.
Are you giving up?
I'm going to college.
I won't give up on my dreams.
Then, unload the child!
That's why I didn't want to...
Tell your father...
My baby
Don't try to kill me on your own.
I know what I'm doing.
You're an idiot.
It's stupid! I know!
But...
If it had been my mom.
I would never have said that.
Dad, I'm sorry.
Today, I'm already...
(expression of) effort or strain
It's a bento... Diet?
No, sir. Saving money.
I know. We have to save money.
Studying to be a curator?
It's costing me money. It's costing me money.
I can't help it.
You really know your stuff.
You're not in the same department?
No, no.
Me. Economy.
Hmmm
（Hey, at that lady's place.
What do you do part-time?
Various.
（Various things?
Oh, Mitsumine-san, hi.
（Yuma and Mr. Nakagawa...
Yuma and Ms. Nakagawa were acquaintances.
What?
Oh, you're a senior in the department.
Oh.
Yes, sir.
Oh, how are you and Yuma?
We've known each other since kindergarten.
What? But the grades...
Yeah, I'm in a lot of different things.
Oh, hey!
Don't eat it without permission.
Yum! Yum!
Could it be...
Have you been forgiven yet?
(Muffled)
Hey, have you eaten yet?
Yeah...
Then buy me a drink.
Yes, sir.
All right.
Bye, Arisu.
See you around.
（Your shoelace is untied.
Ah...
String.
Oh, really?
Will you stop calling her "senior"?
What?
We're already together.
What did you say?
Um...
"You can call me whatever you want.
You can call me whatever you want.
Hmmm...
Then...
Ko-chan?
Ko-chan...
Isn't he cute?
Mr. Koh?
I don't like Mr. Kou.
（Samejima-san.
May I have a word?
（It's fine~!
（This is... a proposal project that I've been working on.
（Oh, yeah...
（I want you to see it.
(Samejima) Okay.
（Yuka Numata's portfolio
Yuka Numata's portfolio.
Yeah, thanks.
（Me too.
Will you let me do it?
What?
With young artists
Curatorial Training Project Work
Oh...
Of course, on a much larger scale.
Sooner or later, it's gonna be all hands on deck.
You're going to have to do it.
I'd like to be a part of this from the very beginning.
I want to be by your side from the start.
I want to watch and learn everything.
please
Yeah, okay. I'll think about it.
please remember me
(incoming vibrator)
Hello, this is Naruse.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Draft beer is ready!
Take your time.
Thank you for transporting the desk the other day.
Thank you very much.
no
Then...
Cheers!
Cheers.
(CHIMES)
Yes, sir.
What?
（Excuse me for interrupting.
（Excuse me for disturbing you.
That was really something.
What? This tower.
Really, I can't do it for too long.
（I know.
I'll be home right after I eat this cake.
excuse me for disturbing (interrupting) you
Uh...
Um...
Yes, ma'am.
I just wanted to make sure.
The kiss in Kanazawa...
Was it really from me?
Yes, sir.
So...
Oh, I beg your pardon.
Oh... no...
And it was only for a moment.
Besides...
Your mother came out.
Huh?
Yes, sir.
This is our house.
Ah...
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your help.
No... it's my pleasure.
I'm sorry to have bothered you.
Oh, no, it's...
Good night.
Pupils?
Yes.
I heard something.
I thought it might be you.
Ah, I'm home.
Oh, no, no, no, no...
You sent it to me?
Thank you.
No.
This is Kase-san.
Thank you very much.
My daughter is indebted to you.
"This is my mother...
I'm sorry, I'm so young...
What?
No, it's not.
Ah...
See you later~
Excuse me.
"Bye-bye.
Oh, my God, I thought you were...
I thought you were a 42-year-old airline employee.
You thought so.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I remembered! I remember!
Well, that's... that's great.
I was out of control that day.
I mean, if I gave you the wrong impression.
I'm sorry.
Oh... well...
I came to Tokyo.
I came here on my own.
Kase-san, you're still young.
You're still young, so it's important to gain experience in various places.
That's a good thing.
You chose this job because
Because you like painting?
Yeah, well...
Kase? → (in Japanese)
Kase, right? That's right!
It's Kase! →
Hey! Hey!
It's the newcomer king, Sobuki Kase.
No, sir.
Also... →
What are you doing now?
Oh, your wife? No.
You were a little younger.
Let's get out of here.
What? You're leaving already?
Oh, yes.
I'm... I'm sorry.
no
Shall we finish our drinks?
Oh...
I'm going home today.
Understood.
excuse me
（Isn't that woman dangerous?
What?
I mean, it's such a great place.
I'm letting you live here.
You even take care of my business.
You're taking care of my business, aren't you?
Would a stranger go that far?
That's true, but...
Maybe... Arisu's baby is what you're after.
Arisu's baby?
What?
I don't know.
When you're 40, your own kids...
I think it might be a little bit difficult.
I think it's a little bit difficult.
Then this single mom shows up.
You take care of her. You owe her.
Eventually, he's going to adopt Arisu's child.
She said she'd adopt him.
Oh, no, no way...
You're not that kind of person, Mr. Naruse.
If Arisu says so.
I'd like to believe you.
But... I'm still worried.
Because it's definitely not normal.
Then give me that baby.
Oh, no, I don't have any.
(Sena and others speaking)
Bye. - Bye.
Bye. Let's play again.
yeah
welcome home
Um... a friend from high school.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Sorry to bother you at this time of night.
I said use it however you want.
I'm in my own house without my knowledge.
I've had strangers in my house without my knowledge.
Not so much.
I don't feel very good about this.
（I'm sorry.
I know we pushed you too hard and...
I raised it.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's late. Go home.
Yes. Excuse me.
greeting used when entering someone's home
I'll send it to you.
I'll do it.
Just go to bed.
I'm sorry
I'm not saying don't invite friends.
But you could have at least called me.
You could have at least called me.
I was going to leave right away...
So you thought you could keep your mouth shut?
I told you he's just a kid.
I don't know if I'll ever be a decent parent.
I don't know if I can be a good parent.
What? If you have something to say.
Say it.
Good morning.
Yes...
Oh...
I forgot...
You forgot.
Okay, I'm going to start the lecture.
I'm home!
(cell phone ringing)
Yeah...
Yes, ma'am.
I'm Naruse.
Oh...
no matter how hard one may try (one is unable to) (with negative verb)
Still a friend's house?
No...
Apartment?
Look outside.
What?
Good morning!
What? You bought this?
Yes, it's inconvenient without a car, isn't it?
When the baby has a sudden fever.
Thank you.
Yes, breakfast.
What?
Did Mr. Naruse make this?
Yes.
Eh...
Wow...
Oh, wow.
Oh, but what about Naruse-san?
don't worry
It's huge...
Oh, wow...
Yeah...
That was a delicious meal (said after meals)
I'm not gonna ask you.
I'm not going to ask you what you think of the food.
Yes, sir.
In exchange, I'll make you breakfast tomorrow.
You make it.
Yes, sir.
Thanks for dinner.
Hi!
Oh...
Feels good.
Speaking of which...
Have you picked a name yet?
What?
The child's name
Oh, no...
You're too quick.
Why not?
To the baby
When you talk to her.
I'd rather have a name.
It's better to have a name.
Oh...
What's up?
No... something just now...
I felt it move.
Baby?
Where? Where is it?
Is it my imagination?
But... it moved, right?
Maybe...
You're alive.
You're doing great. You're alive.
Good.
Name...
I've made up my mind.
What?
sea
good name
That's a good name.